AoM Records 5289
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series SERIES I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series E. COMMITTEE RECORDS.
    - Sub-Series 1 All-Academy Standing Committees
      - Site Selection Committee, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Site Selection Committee, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Sub-Series 2. Other All-Academy Committees
      - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1948-1968 (Box 13, Folder 22)
        Includes correspondence regarding the constitutional revision; committee roster; drafts of the proposed changes in the constitution; vote results on new constitution
      - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 23)
        Includes purpose of the committee; 1970 report of the committee; 1971 proposed amendments to the constitution
      - Committee Assignments, 1952-1990 (Box 13, Folder 24)
        made by the President and approved by the Board of Governors
      - Committee on Awards, 1980-1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Centennial Committee, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Media Relations Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Media Relations Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Research Committee, Research and Publications Committee, 1949-1961 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Research Committee, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 34)
        Includes study: "The Research Interests and Activities of the Academy's Membership"
      - Research Committee, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Committee on Regional Divisions, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Ad-Hoc Committee on Divisional Proceedings, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - Comparative Administration Task Force, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - Archives Committee, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - Publication Editors Nominating Committee, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - Board of Governors (BOG) Task Force and Policy Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 41)
        Examined the Academy's current issues in governance, structuring, and budgeting
      - BOG Task Force and Professional Divisions Policy Committee, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
        Addressed the Academy's problem of leadership and membership separation
      - BOG Task Force and Policy Committee, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 43)
        Includes responses of the professional divisions to the report of the 1977 78 Task Force
      - Newsletter Associate Editor Search Committee, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - Incorporation Committee, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - Search Committee, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - Public Information Task Force, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - Editor Search and Award Committee, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - Task Force on the Academy of Management Professional, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - International Programs Committee, 1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - Outcome Measurement Task Force, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 51)
        Includes Task Force objectives, minutes of meetings, and correspondence
      - Outcome Measurement Task Force, preliminary report, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Outcome Measurement Task Force, revised report, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      - Management Practitioners Task Force, 1988-1991 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      - Task Force on a Code of Ethics, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      - Task Force on a Code of Ethics, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 56)
      - Integration of Structures and Activities Task Force, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      - Consulting Group on Academy Growth and Structure, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      - Committee and Task Force Activities, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 59)
        notes kept by Academy President
      - Status of Minorities Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 60)
      - Search Committee, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      - Task Force on Member Assessment, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 62)
        Includes purpose and preliminary results of the questionnaire
  - Sub-Series F. Regional Divisions.
    Regional divisions function autonomously from the National Academy of Management, though they augment and complement its activities. They hold their own meetings and programs and develop their own membership requirements, Constitutions, and operating guidelines. There are five regional divisions: Eastern Academy of Management (EAM); Midwest Academy of Management; Southern Management Association, (SMA); Southwest Division; and Western Academy of Management.
    - Sub-Series 1. Eastern Academy of Management (EAM)
      - EAM, Constitution, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - EAM, Founding correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - EAM, Board of Governors (BOG) Meeting, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
        Mar-69
      - EAM, BOG, correspondence, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - EAM, Annual Business Meeting, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
        May-78
      - EAM, BOG Meeting, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
        May-79
      - Eastern Academy of Management (EAM), Board of Governors (BOG), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
        May-80
      - EAM, Annual Business Meeting, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - EAM, BOG and Annual Business Meeting, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - EAM, BOG Meeting, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 10)
        May-82
      - EAM, Annual Business Meeting, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - EAM, BOG, correspondence, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - EAM, BOG Meeting, minutes, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 13)
        May-89
      - EAM, Annual Business Meeting, minutes, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - EAM Directory, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - EAM, BOG Meeting, minutes, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 16)
        May-90
      - EAM, BOG Meeting, minutes, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - EAM, Annual Business Meeting, minutes, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - EAM, BOG Meeting, minutes, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 19-20)
        May-91
      - EAM, Annual Business Meeting, minutes, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - EAM Directory, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - EAM Directory, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - EAM, BOG Meeting, minutes, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 24)
        May-93
      - EAM, Annual Business Meeting, minutes, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - EAM Directory, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - EAM, BOG Meeting, minutes, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 27-28)
        May-94
      - EAM, Annual Business Meeting, minutes, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Eastern Academy of Management (EAM), Board of Governors (BOG) Meeting, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 30-31)
        May-96
      - EAM, Annual Business Meeting, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - EAM, Job Descriptions, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 34a)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 42)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 43)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 44)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 45)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 46)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 47)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 48)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 49)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 50)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 51)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 52)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 53)
      - EAM International Conference Proceedings, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 54)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 55)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 56)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 57)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 58)
      - EAM International Conference. Call for Papers, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 59)
      - EAM International Conference Proceedings, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 60)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 61)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 62)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - EAM International Conference correspondence, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - EAM International Conference Proceedings, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - EAM International Conference correspondence, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - EAM International Conference Proceedings, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - EAM International Conference correspondence, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - EAM International Conference Proceedings, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - EAM International Conference correspondence, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - EAM Annual Meeting, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - EAM Proceedings, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - EAM International Conference (Box 16, Folder 3)
        Call for Papers and program
      - EAM International Conference Proceedings, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - EAM Annual Meeting (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - EAM Membership Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
        Includes membership brochures and member list
      - EAM Membership Committee, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
        member list
      - EAM Membership Committee, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - EAM Nominations Committee, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
        correspondence and ballot
      - EAM Placement Committee, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - EAM Small College and University Network, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
        report and newsletter
      - EAM Newsletters, 1992-1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Sub-Series 2. Midwest Academy of Management
      - Midwest, Constitution, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 15)
        Including general correspondence, meeting announcements and calls for papers, and meeting programs
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Midwest Proceedings, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Midwest Proceedings, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 25)
        and Proceedings
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Midwest Proceedings, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Midwest Proceedings, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Midwest Annual Meeting, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - Midwest, Presidents' Newsletters (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - Midwest, Jerry G. Hunt files, 1969-1993 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - Midwest, Membership Directory, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - Midwest, Nominating Committee, 1988-1994 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - Midwest, Placement Committee (Box 16, Folder 37)
        undated
      - Midwest, Internationalizing Workshop, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 38)
        at 1988 Annual Meeting
      - Midwest, Newsletters, 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Sub-Series 3. Southern Management Association (SMA)
      - SMA, Revised Constitution, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - SMA, Board of Governors, correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - SMA Annual Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - SMA, Evaluation Report of Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - SMA Annual Meeting, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - SMA Annual Meeting, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - SMA Executive Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - SMA Membership Committee, 1973-1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - deleted (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - SMA Nominations Committee, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - SMA Newsletters, 1986-1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - SMA, Journal of Management, correspondence, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - SMA, Journal of Management, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
        Fall 1979
    - Sub-Series 4. Southwest Division
      - Southwest, Constitution and By-Laws, revisions, 1982-1990 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Southwest, Annual Business Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Southwest, Annual Business Meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Southwest, Annual Business Meeting, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Southwest, Annual Business Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Southwest Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 19)
        includes general correspondence, meeting announcements and calls for papers, and meeting programs
      - Southwest, Symposium Proposals, Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Southwest Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Southwest Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 22)
        Doctoral Student/Young Professor Consortium
      - Southwest Annual Meeting, 1989-1994 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Southwest Division, Membership Reports, 1981-1991 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Southwest, Nominating Committee, 1982-1994 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Southwest, Best Paper Award, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Southwest, Newsletters, 1989-1994 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Sub-Series 5. Western Academy of Management (WAM)
      - WAM Annual Meeting, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 28)
        including general correspondence, meeting announcements and calls for papers, and meeting programs
      - WAM Annual Meeting, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - WAM Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - WAM Annual Meeting, 1983-1988 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - WAM, First International Conference, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - WAM Annual Meeting, 1990-1994 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - WAM, Newsletters, 1986-1990 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Regional Divisions, National Report (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Regional Divisions, National Coordination (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series G. PROFESSIONAL DIVISIONS.
    Organized alphabetically by Division name. The Professional Divisions are the primary source of national-level affiliation for most members of the Academy.
    - Sub-Series 1. Business, Policy, and Strategy Division
      - Governance, Budget, 5 year Review (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Governance, Constitution, Professional Division Policy Statement (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Governance, Financial Records, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Governance, Report to Professional Division Review Committee (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Annual Meeting, Professional Papers, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Planning Materials (Box 17, Folder 39)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Planning Materials (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Planning Materials (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Planning Materials, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - Doctoral Consortium, correspondence, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Applicant Vitae, Resumes, Letter of Recommendation (Box 17, Folder 45)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Applicant Vitae, Resumes, Letter of Recommendation (Box 17, Folder 46)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Applicant Vitae, Resumes, Letter of Recommendation (Box 17, Folder 47)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Applicant Correspondence and Participant List (Box 17, Folder 48)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Faculty Participants (Box 17, Folder 49)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Faculty Biographical Information (Box 17, Folder 50)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Discussion Groups (Box 17, Folder 51)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Readings (Box 17, Folder 52)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Evaluations (Box 17, Folder 53)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Evaluations (Box 17, Folder 54)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Compiled Student Evaluations (Box 17, Folder 55)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Compiled Faculty Evaluations (Box 17, Folder 56)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Thank You Letters and Bills (Box 17, Folder 57)
      - Annual Meeting, Doctoral Consortium, Task Force Report (Box 17, Folder 57a)
      - Annual Meeting, New Faculty Consortium, Task Force, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 57b)
      - Annual Meeting, Dissertation Award Information (Box 17, Folder 57c)
      - Doctoral Consortium, Annual Meeting Planning Materials, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 58)
      - Executive Committee Mid-Winter Meeting, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 58a)
      - Executive Officers, Midwinter Meeting and Division Officers (Box 17, Folder 58b)
      - Executive Officers, Letter from Incoming Chair, Theory Paper Solicitation, and Structure of Ph.D. Program (Box 17, Folder 58c)
      - Executive Officers, Executive Committee Meeting (Box 17, Folder 58d)
      - Executive Officers, Annual Meeting, List of BPP Members, Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 58e)
      - Executive Officers, Harrigan, Executive Committee (Box 17, Folder 58f)
      - Executive Officers, Harrigan, Annual Meetings (Box 17, Folder 58g)
      - Executive Officers, Harrigan, Treasurer Reports (Box 17, Folder 58h)
      - Executive Officers, Harrigan, Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 58i)
      - Elections Committee, Ballots, biographies, and results, 1979-1984 (Box 17, Folder 59)
      - Elections Committee, Ballots and biographies, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence, BPS net e-email information (Box 17, Folder 61)
      - Correspondence, General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 61a)
      - Correspondence, Division Report (Box 17, Folder 61b)
      - Correspondence, Statistics (Box 17, Folder 61c)
      - Competitive Awards, Free Press Award for Outstanding Dissertation (Box 17, Folder 61d)
      - Name Change, General Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 61e)
    - Sub-Series 2. Careers Division
      - Membership Committee, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Membership Committee, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
        Networking List of Members
      - Election Committee, Ballots and Biographies, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Election Committee, Ballots and Biographies, 1992-1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Newsletters, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Newsletters, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Newsletters, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Newsletters, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Newsletters, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Newsletters, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Newsletters, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Newsletters, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Newsletters, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Newsletters, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Newsletters, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Newsletters, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Sub-Series 3. Entrepreneurship Division
      - Governance, correspondence (Box 18, Folder 19a)
      - Governance, surveys (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Governance, 5-year Review (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Annual Meeting, Report, Pre-convention Announcements, 1982-1989 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Annual Meeting, Call for Papers, Pre-convention program, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Annual Meeting, Pre-convention Program, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning, Pre-convention program and registration, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning Correspondence, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Membership Committee, Prospective Members Sheet, Division Information Sheet (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Elections Committee, Ballots and Biographies, 1990-1996 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Small Business Forum (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, Call for Papers, Survey, Symposium Registration (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, Faculty Position Announcements, Gateway Series Registration, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - Newsletters, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 33)
      - Newsletters, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 34)
      - Newsletters, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 35)
        dates unknown, Volume 4.1 - 5.2
      - Newsletters, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 36)
        May 1990 - December 1990
      - Newsletters, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 37)
        April 1991 - Fall 1991
      - Newsletters, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 38)
        Spring 1992 - Fall 1992
      - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 39)
        Spring 1993 - Fall 1993
      - Newsletters, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 40)
        Fall 1994 - Spring 1994
      - Newsletters, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 41)
        Spring 1996 - Summer 1996
      - Newsletters, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 42)
        Fall 1996 - Spring 1997
      - Governance, Strategic Committee Report and 5-year Survey (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Sub-Series 4. Health Care Administration Division
      - Governance, Survey Results, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 44)
      - Governance, Origins of the Division (Box 18, Folder 45)
      - Annual Meeting, Planning Procedure (Box 18, Folder 46)
      - Annual Meeting, Registration, Invitations, and Schedules (Box 18, Folder 47)
      - Elections Committee, Nominations, Ballots and Biographies, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence, Congratulation letter and Faculty Opening (Box 18, Folder 49)
      - Newsletters, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 50)
        September 1981-November 1982
      - Newsletters, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 51)
        March 1983 - November 1983
      - Newsletters, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 52)
        April 1984 - November 1984
      - Newsletters, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 53)
        April 1985 - November 1985
      - Newsletters, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 54)
      - Newsletters, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 55)
      - Newsletters, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 56)
      - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 57)
      - Newsletters, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 58)
      - Newsletters, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 59)
      - Newsletters, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 60)
      - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 61)
      - Newsletters, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 62)
      - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 63)
      - Newsletters, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 64)
      - Newsletters, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Sub-Series 5. Human Resources Division
      - Governance, Division Review, Questionnaire, Goals (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Annual Meeting, Doctoral Consortium, Symposium Description (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Membership Committee, Request for Membership Data (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Elections Committee, Nominations, Ballots, and Biographies (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Elections Committee, Nominations, Ballots, and Biographies (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - ASPA Call for Proposals, New Journals, Awards (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 11)